Good Afternoon Rhymes
that welcome back to my YouTube channel today
was Winner Friday now I am out to
collect some medicine important medicines had
ordered online
their delivery boy is not available whatsapp imo is working so
you can't do it yet the
record regarding medicine is
completely gone so Dasha am going
personality factor in the morning how are you
guys in this real world I at least on my
Instagram many people asked that
sir why did you focus only on crops you [ __ ] the
secretaries you should have bought Activa or
Jupiter so let me tell you today
why did I focus on animals I ignored them where I will
tell them the real thing so before this I was
identified so I had done a
lot of setup from Yamaha service center the service they provided
the type they all use was
very good so I
never had any complaint with you their service
network was very good and when my cousin had
Activa then you people
who also have Activa will be
able to relate to this  That Activa clutch is changed after 10000 to
15000 kms, the
service center people have to
sweat a lot, during this time you can easily torture
it and I have had it for around a year and a half
and till now there is
no problem with its plus, the build quality and
deflection of the Activa is
much better, I agree that the
BSP is less in some points, the
DSP power of the Festival is more but
things of Activa scooter, take a motor motor
sports bike, there is
less power in some points, it is
not clear that much but which thing of the English is
more refined, which thing is more
durable, then I am afraid, I
seized the machines and it also cost you around ₹2000 more
in those days when I bought this
Activa, it was 2017, I am talking about 110 cc,
sit down, I had taken a little cost, come
I will make a detailed video in which I will
show the complete comparison of Activa and Activa
and will also give its ownership review, I am saying
that I have  Why did you do that,
what maintenance have I seen till then
and what is my average delay, I will get
everything, everything, everything in my videos,
so forget you, nice, and now we are
going to
clean the lock, a reply, don't forget to follow your
Instagram, the Instagram handle is coming down,
you should follow that,
this has come, our National Highway-12,
Grand Trunk Road, GT Road, Ashwin, nowadays a
lot of construction is going on, but the
road which has been built now, bro Vaidya, I would
like to tell you about the condition of the road which has been built,
and now should I tell him that its
a next level road which is being built, it has been
built with a list and the work has been done at a very fast pace and
it will go straight from Delhi to Panipat, it is 9 inches long,
Ajay has got it
[Music]
MP3, you must be able to
see now, he used to
live in one tune, from that side he used to teach
all his people, party halls, gardens,
banquets, etc., so he used to
stay here so much, but since the government has come, they have
made rules for all this, approval is required on MS Word,
notification comes  It has become a
ruin type place, look at it
and I have heard that there was a time when there was
not even space to take out a scooter here, parking, parking, parking, a
submarine, mostly in Delhi, so marriages used to take place on
this event here,
around 1975, if
not wrong then we are here, he had a job, all this, parties
etc. were done to cool down, it has
happened that
Ajay has
taken medicine, um, the best way to have fun is
that Sudhir, if you want a
video to be made on any specific topic, then please do
DM me on Instagram or tell
me by commenting in the comment section of this video
and the next video of Chor will be
about that and I will put one and a half clock on the pan,
subscribe in 365 days, definitely
tune in to this channel for more
videos and
now we are going straight to our home,
which all the things have been happening for
some moments since a farmer is sitting here
and the farmers' movement, Chandra Singh Gohil, all the
tricks etc. are all from here and
you can watch S2 here  It is happening, do it, on
one side peace, do it, do it, do it, I want to
hear it, because of such a
busy schedule Feb 22, I have to get
my scooter serviced, it is
pending for at least 15 days,
but once I get free from all my work, the
first thing I will do is service it,
Vikas, until we do not play with our machines
and take care of ourselves,
Reddy, buying a bike, buying a scooter is a
wrong thing, but maintaining it is our
own wish and until we do
not maintain any machine, it will
not play with us for long
and you people also, none of us
want to be in the middle of the road, saying look, look,
look, so do it
[Music]
that we
do it,
I am the people of the sun, that's all, if you liked
my blog, liked my content, then
please please like this
video and subscribe to my channel, subscribe to the channel,
guide and also press the bell icon,
and the bell icon, nothing else,
if friends, by issues meet tomorrow
Thank you Thank you for the evening is back with a new content on the blog